You've been caught
red-handed for smuggling.
The goods will be confiscated,
and you will be
taken into custody.
What was that?
Looks like some trouble.
I'm gonna check it out!
Hey!
I'm gonna lend a hand!
There's no need for that!
You should learn to accept
the generosity of others.
What you're offering is called
an unwelcome favor.
You're not cute.
I'd prefer you didn't
think that I'm cute.
I'm not letting you get away!
If they're in a car, there're
only certain routes they can take.
We can catch up by
using the back roads!
Wh-What?
Hurry up.
I know!
There's some
trouble at the harbor.
Trouble?
Here you go.
Lasagna!
I've been waiting for you!
Thank you for the meal!
Hey!
Milady.
What is it now, Luca?
Th-The party tonight
is a very special one.
We should start heading
back to the mansion.
There'll be plenty of time,
even after we finish our patrol.
Yes, but...
You'll also need time to change.
Found you!
Libertá?
That idiot.
He's too reckless.
Nova.
Felicitá.
Don't move, Libertá.
Debito!
Jump, Libertá!
Are you serious?!
That's dangerous, Dante!
No need to worry.
See?
Pace.
Move!
I-I surrender.
And that settles that.
Dante,
what are we going
to do about the car?
I was about to die!
Your actions are too bold!
Well, I am bald.
Just kidding!
Let's go.
Who are those people?
That was intense.
Is this your first
time here, boys?
I'm curious if this
is the first time
you've been to the
trade island of Regalo.
Y-Yes.
Then let me tell you.
Clean out your
ears and listen well.
They are the vigilante organization
that protects Regalo Island,
the Arcana Famiglia.
Milady.
What did you just say?
You mustn't.
This isn't just
some ordinary party.
Milady.
Everyone is waiting for you.
Milady!
What's the matter, Luca?
You're not attending the
party in those clothes, are you?
Yeah.
You mustn't!
Today is—
Papa's birthday, right?
Let's go, Fukulota.
She used to be
much more obedient.
Maybe there's a problem
with how you raised her.
Huh?
Indeed, you were her
attendant since she was little.
Huh?
It's all your fault, Luca.
Huh?!
We're going to be late, Luca!
Right away, Milady!
What's wrong?
What are you wearing, Bambina?
We were all looking forward
to seeing you in a dress.
What's wrong with
what I'm wearing?
Luca, do your job
as her attendant!
Yeah! It's bad enough that we're
constantly surrounded by just guys!
But I...
But I wanted her
to wear a dress, too!
However,
if something were to
happen, it's probably better
for her to be wearing something
less restrictive than a dress.
You've got a point.
It's easier to admire
Bambina's long, beautiful legs
with what she's got on now.
Do you have a
leg fetish, shorty?
We may agree on something.
How stupid.
Huh?
You're not wearing
a dress, Princess?
What's wrong?
Princess?
Your face is red.
Ouch.
What the hell was that for?
Wh-What the hell
did I do, Princess?!
Jolly.
It's because you were
thinking bad things.
What do you mean, "bad things?"
This shouldn't need
explaining again, but we have all
made a deal with Tarocco
to gain our Arcana powers.
For example, you, Libertá,
have the first card,
Il Matto: the Fool.
R-Right.
Nova, just like you have the
13th card, La Morte: Death.
You don't have to
explain all of this now.
Milady made a deal
with the sixth card,
Gli Amanti: the Lovers.
Her power, by that I
mean her Arcana power,
is the power to see
into others' hearts.
Then...
But I just saw it by chance.
Yes. Arcana powers use
emotions as their foundation.
The reason you don't have
control over your powers yet, Milady,
is because you're
still just a child.
Please do not touch the lady.
She read Libertá's heart?
Does that mean you were thinking of Milady in unbecoming
ways?! Idiot The hell do you mean, "unbecoming ways?!"
W-Well...
My apologies, Milady...
My condolences.
Hey!
Dante's going to
give his greeting.
Gentlemen,
I would like to thank everyone
for showing up despite
your busy schedules,
for the sake of our Arcana
Famiglia's "Papa," Mondo.
We would like to start
with a word from Papa.
The head of our family!
Glory to Arcana!
Gentlemen.
Thank you for gathering today.
I am celebrating my
59th birthday today.
The reason I have gotten
this far is because of all of you.
Our Regalo Island
has overcome many hardships.
Raids from smugglers,
occupation from foreign countries,
lack of goods,
oppression from a
tyrant, epidemics...
Once you start
counting, there's no end.
But we were able to overcome
all of this with our familial bond,
and with the Arcana powers.
But I've gotten to that age.
I'm starting to think
about retirement.
Papa?
Therefore,
I am considering choosing
someone to take my place.
In two months, we will be
holding the Arcana Duello.
Arcana Duello?
It will be a fight where all those
with Arcana powers will participate
to determine who has the
strongest Arcana powers.
I, the 21st card, Il Mondo:
The World, hereby swear
to give the victor
the title of "Papa"
and grant their wish.
One more thing.
The winner will marry
my daughter, Felicitá.
Marry the Princess?
What are you thinking, Papa?
What? What does that mean?
Well, this will get interesting.
What is it, Felicitá?
Do you have any concerns?
I don't want to get married.
You chose with your own free
will to join the Arcana Famiglia.
This is the rule of the family.
Meaning, you
have to do as I say.
Am I wrong?
You will become the new
Mama, and support the family.
What's the reason
for this, Papa?
There is a reason.
However, I need
not explain myself.
Oh?
If you don't want
to follow orders,
challenge me here and win.
Papa!
That's impossible!
Just shut up.
This looks interesting.
Is that all your
kick has to offer?
Princess...
I will choose...
my own path!
You haven't the right to
choose your own path...
in your present condition!
Princess!
Milady!
If you're just going
to sit there and glare,
a little child can do that, too.
Why not try shedding
a tear or two, as well?
You may be able to
earn the pity of the men
who are going to participate
in the Arcana Duello.
You're robbing the
Princess of her freedom.
How can you call
yourself a father?!
What are you doing, Libertá?
Well done, Libertá the fool!
Your careless, no regard
outbursts are fantastic!
Don't instigate him, Debito!
Are you saying you can't
follow orders either, Libertá?
That's right!
Then defeat me,
right here, right now.
What's the matter?
Are you scared of making a
fool of yourself, like Felicitá?
There's no guarantee...
that I'm going to
make a fool of myself!
Libertá!
Nova!
Papa is the father
of our family, as well.
I won't condone any harm
toward our father.
Move!
Debito?
Very perceptive.
I made a deal with the ninth
card, L'eremita: the Hermit.
So your powers are to
make yourself invisible.
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Would you let me
go, you meathead!
I understand how you feel, but
it's not good if
you disobey Papa.
Pace has
a deal with the 11th
card, La Forza: Strength.
His strength is overwhelming.
No one can oppose it.
Let go.
Let me go!
What?
How pitiful.
If you want to free my daughter,
then you need to
win the Arcana Duello.
I told you.
I will grant any wish.
Felicitá.
Mama.
There is a way for
you to win as well.
You're going to choose
your own path, right?
The Wheel of Fortune
has started turning,
opposing the guidance
of the Tarocco.
There's no way I'd get married,
but I wouldn't mind being
bound with Bambina.
Debito, how dare you?!
I'm sure every day would be
fun if the Princess were my wife.
Pace, you, too?
Then what are you going to do
about the Arcana Duello, Luca?
I will cheer on Milady!
However, Papa said,
that everyone with Arcana
powers will be fighting.
Bambina is a heartless woman.
However, that can
be rather charming.
Mondo has thought up
something rather absurd.
I'm getting all excited
thinking of Milady as my bride.
Jolly, you...
What? Do you think I'll lose?
Unfortunately, that's
not going to happen.
That is, if I take
this seriously.
Libertá.
Don't worry, Princess!
What?
I'm going to win this and
take the title of "Papa."
Then...
I'll be your bride?
No!
Th-That's not what I meant!
Um...
Anyway, it means you'll
regain your freedom.
Right?
That's right.
You may end up my bride...
But that's sort of
weird to think about.
You're so oblivious.
What do you mean by
"oblivious," you chickpea.
Don't call me a chickpea!
You can barely control
your Arcana powers,
yet you're foolish enough to
say you'll win the Arcana Duello.
If that's not oblivious,
then what is it?
I made the decision
to live by this sword.
So I have no need
for Arcana powers.
You truly are oblivious.
But you can't use your
Arcana powers either.
I've never seen you
use your Arcana powers.
Don't compare me with you!
Don't worry, Felicitá.
If I were to win, I'll
wish not to marry you.
That means if either of us wins,
then Princess will be free!
The likelihood of you
winning is rather slim.
The hell did you
say, you chickpea?!
The truth.
And don't call me a chickpea.
Ciao! So, next time's story
involves Princess and me
looking for the
owner of a lost cat?
It should be a lot of fun since
it's just me and the Princess...
What? The chickpea's
coming, too? Ugh...